The Hudson River Environmental Society Collection
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 7. Legal Documents, 7; 3 linear feet 16 - 18 634 - 791
  - Legal Papers, 7.1
    - Legal Papers, Box 16; 7.1
      - Proposal for a Further Biological and Engineering Study Program..., 679 (Box 16)
      - Responses to Consolidated Edison’s Request of Oct. 20, 1972, 680 (Box 16)
      - Response to Dr. Lawler’s Additional Testimony 03/30/1973, 681 (Box 16)
      - Response to Interrogatory of Hudson River Fisherman’s Assoc. Myron Karman, 682 (Box 16)
      - Response to Interrogatory of Hudson River Fisherman’s Association on Supplemental Staff Testimony on the Feasibility of a Fish Hatchery..., 683 (Box 16)
      - Response to Position of HRFA on Research Program Proposed by Con Edison, 684 (Box 16)
      - Requests for Information in Connection with Con. Edison’s Application for Amendment of License DPR-26, 685 (Box 16)
      - Staff Responses to Interrogatories for Dr. C. P. Goodyear re Staff Comments on Applicant’s Research Program, 686 (Box 16)
      - Statement: Vermilye, Kitty, 687 (Box 16)
      - Summary of Work Done and Expected Testimony W. Van Winkle, 02/02/1977, 688 (Box 16)
      - Summary Proceedings - Hudson Valley Regional Land Use Planning Conference, 1990, 689 (Box 16)
      - Transcript Corrections Feb 14 - June 29, 1978, 690 (Box 16)
      - Transcript Errors, 691 (Box 16)
      - Transcripts: Highlights and Table of Contents (1), 692 (Box 16)
      - Transcripts: Highlights and Table of Contents (2), 693 (Box 16)
      - Transmittal: Marcellus, Kenneth, 694 (Box 16)
      - Transmittal: Marcellus, Kenneth 04/14/1978, 695 (Box 16)
      - Transmittal: Marcellus, Kenneth 05/12/1978, 696 (Box 16)
      - Transmittal: Marcellus, Kenneth 10/12/1978, 697 (Box 16)
      - Trial Memorandum - Alleged Violations of Sections 17-0501, 17-0511, and 11-0505... by GEC, 698 (Box 16)
  - Testimony, 7.2
    - Testimony, Box 17; 7.2
      Testimony
      - Bayless, Jack D., 699 (Box 17)
      - Baxter, Bernard Z., Jr., 700 (Box 17)
      - Bremer, Herman C., Dr. Henri M. Gueron, and Edward J. Brown, 701 (Box 17)
      - Brunett, Richard E., 702 (Box 17)
      - Bzura, John J., 703 (Box 17)
      - Clark, John, 704 (Box 17)
      - Clark, John R. (duplicate), 705 (Box 17)
      - Clark, John R. (with notes), 706 (Box 17)
      - Comninellis, Eustratios, 707 (Box 17)
      - Crane, Robert F., 708 (Box 17)
      - Davis, Atlton P., Jr., 709 (Box 17)
      - Fullerton, Frank M., 710 (Box 17)
      - Goodyear, Dr. C. P. - 02/22/1973, 711 (Box 17)
      - Goodyear, Dr. C. P. - 02/22/1973 Con Edison’s Research Program at Indian Point, 712 (Box 17)
      - Goodyear, Dr. C. P. - 02/22/1973 Dissolved Oxygen Concentrations in the Hudson..., 713 (Box 17)
      - Goodyear, Dr. C. P. - 02/22/1973 Effects of Indian Point Units 1 and 2 on Hudson River Fish Population, 714 (Box 17)
      - Goodyear, Dr. C. P. - 02/22/1973 Factors Which Influence the Rate of Growth in Larval Striped Bass, 715 (Box 17)
      - Goodyear, Dr. C. P. - 02/22/1973 Mathematical Model Used by the Staff..., 716 (Box 17)
      - Goodyear, Dr. C. P. - 02/22/1973 Staff Comments on Applicant’s Research Program, 717 (Box 17)
      - Goodyear, Dr. C. P. - 02/22/1973 Susceptibility of Larvae to the Intake of Indian Point 2, 718 (Box 17)
      - Goodyear, Dr. C. P. and Dr. C. C. Coutant - 02/22/1973, 719 (Box 17)
      - Goodyear, Dr. C. P. and Dr. J. S. Mattice - 03/01/1973, 720 (Box 17)
      - Goodyear, Dr. C. P. - 04/09/1973, 721 (Box 17)
      - Goodyear, Dr. C. P. - 04/24/1973, 722 (Box 17)
      - Goodyear, Dr. C. P. - 02/19/1974, 723 (Box 17)
      - Graves, Robert W., 724 (Box 17)
      - Gray, Senator Arthur, 725 (Box 17)
      - Gueron, Dr. Henri M., John J. Szeligowski, and Dr. Thomas L. Englert, 726 (Box 17)
      - Haase, H. Kenneth, 727 (Box 17)
      - Hoffman, Dr. Peter, 728 (Box 17)
      - Jannarone, John R., 729 (Box 17)
      - Kirk, Dr. William L., James B. McLaren, and Jack D. Bayless, 730 (Box 17)
      - Knighton, George, 731 (Box 17)
      - Lauer, Gerald J., 732 (Box 17)
      - Lawler, Dr. John P. - 04/05/1972, 733 (Box 17)
      - Lawler, Dr. John P. - 10/30/1972, 734 (Box 17)
      - Lawler, Dr. John P. - 10/30/1972, 735 (Box 17)
      - Lawler, Dr. John P. - 02/05/1973, 736 (Box 17)
      - Lawler, Dr. John P. - 03/03/1973, 737 (Box 17)
      - Lawler, Dr. John P. - 03/05/1973, 738 (Box 17)
      - Lawler, Dr. John P. - 03/30/1973, 739 (Box 17)
      - Lawler, Dr. John P. - 10/1974, 740 (Box 17)
      - Liede, Henry H., 741 (Box 17)
      - McFadden, James T., 742 (Box 17)
      - McFadden, James T., Dr, John P. Lawler, Dr. Thomas L. Englert, etc., 743 (Box 17)
      - McFadden, James T., and Dr. Kenneth L. Marcellus, 744 (Box 17)
      - McFadden, James T., and Thomas Cannon, 745 (Box 17)
      - McFadden, James T., Thomas L. Englert, Ronald J. Klauda, etc., 746 (Box 17)
      - Morgan, Dr. Raymond P., II., 747 (Box 17)
      - Morgan, Dr. Raymond P., II. (duplicate), 748 (Box 17)
      - Newman, Carl L., 749 (Box 17)
      - Palensky, John R., 750 (Box 17)
      - Perry, David F., 751 (Box 17)
      - Prichard, D. W., 752 (Box 17)
      - Raney, Edward C., 753 (Box 17)
      - Rider, Charles E. and Ezra A. Jodidio, 754 (Box 17)
      - Saila, Dr. Saul B., 755 (Box 17)
      - Sampson, David S., 756 (Box 17)
      - Schaefer, Richard H., 757 (Box 17)
      - Schuster, Carl N. Jr., 758 (Box 17)
      - Schuster, Carl N. Jr. (duplicate), 759 (Box 17)
      - Seddon, John W., 760 (Box 17)
      - Shepley, Jack M., 761 (Box 17)
      - Skinner, Peter, 762 (Box 17)
      - Staff (Supplemental), 763 (Box 17)
      - Stein, Stuart W., 764 (Box 17)
      - Tucker, Richard J., 765 (Box 17)
      - Waxman, Dr. Jeffrey B., Dr. Kenneth L. Marcellus, Dr. Ronald J. Klaudo, etc., 766 (Box 17)
      - Winer, Bette M., 767 (Box 17)
      - Woodbury, 768 (Box 17)
      - Yang, Kuo Hua, 769 (Box 17)
      - Yang, Kuo Hua (duplicate), 770 (Box 17)
  - Stenographers’ Report, 7.3
    - Stenographers’ Report, Box 18; 7.3
      Stenographers’ Report
      - Stenographers’ Report: Pages 3061-3150, 771 (Box 18)
      - Stenographers’ Report: Pages 3151-3258, 772 (Box 18)
      - Stenographers’ Report: Pages 3260-3300, 773 (Box 18)
      - Stenographers’ Report: Pages 3301-3400, 774 (Box 18)
      - Stenographers’ Report: Pages 3401-3458, 775 (Box 18)
      - Stenographers’ Report: Pages 3459-3600, 776 (Box 18)
      - Stenographers’ Report: Pages 3601-3700, 777 (Box 18)
      - Stenographers’ Report: Pages 3701-3800, 778 (Box 18)
      - Stenographers’ Report: Pages 3801-3852, 779 (Box 18)
      - Stenographers’ Report: Pages 3853-3949, 780 (Box 18)
      - Stenographers’ Report: Pages 3950-4049, 781 (Box 18)
      - Stenographers’ Report: Pages 4050-4105, 782 (Box 18)
      - Stenographers’ Report: Pages 4106-4200, 783 (Box 18)
      - Stenographers’ Report: Pages 4201-4301, 784 (Box 18)
      - Stenographers’ Report: Pages 4302-4399, 785 (Box 18)
      - Stenographers’ Report: Pages 4400-4488, 786 (Box 18)
      - Stenographers’ Report: Pages 4490-4599, 787 (Box 18)
      - Stenographers’ Report: Pages 4600-4699, 788 (Box 18)
      - Stenographers’ Report: Pages 4700-4799, 789 (Box 18)
      - Stenographers’ Report: Pages 4800-4887, 790 (Box 18)
      - Stenographers’ Report: Pages 4888-4917, 791 (Box 18)
- 8. Chronological Files, 8; 1 linear foot 19 792 - 825
  Files and clippings collected and organized by the Hudson River Environmental Society relating to research, accomplishments, and environmental interests.
  Chronologically
  - Chronological Files, Box 19; 8
    Files and clippings organized chronologically by HRES
    - 79-101 - 79-103, 792 (Box 19)
    - 79-104, 793 (Box 19)
    - 79-105 - 79-114, 794 (Box 19)
    - 79-115 - 79-125, 795 (Box 19)
    - 79-169 - 79-174, 796 (Box 19)
    - 79-180 - 79-199, 797 (Box 19)
    - 79-200 - 79-213, 798 (Box 19)
    - 79-214 - 79-217, 799 (Box 19)
    - 79-218, 800 (Box 19)
    - 79-220 - 79-222, 801 (Box 19)
    - 79-223 - 79-230, 802 (Box 19)
    - 79-231 - 79-240, 803 (Box 19)
    - 79-241 - 79-250, 804 (Box 19)
    - 79-251 - 79-258, 805 (Box 19)
    - 79-260 - 79-267, 806 (Box 19)
    - 79-268 - 79-279, 807 (Box 19)
    - 79-280 - 79-288, 808 (Box 19)
    - 79-289, 809 (Box 19)
    - 79-290 - 79-299, 810 (Box 19)
    - 79-300 - 79-309, 811 (Box 19)
    - 79-310 - 79-319, 812 (Box 19)
    - 79-320 - 79-329, 813 (Box 19)
    - 79-330, 814 (Box 19)
    - 79-331, 815 (Box 19)
    - 79-332 - 79-337, 816 (Box 19)
    - 79-338, 817 (Box 19)
    - 79-339, 818 (Box 19)
    - 79-340 - 79-353, 819 (Box 19)
    - 79-354 - 79-359, 820 (Box 19)
    - 79-360, 821 (Box 19)
    - 79-361 - 79-368, 822 (Box 19)
    - 79-369, 823 (Box 19)
    - 79-370 - 79-380, 824 (Box 19)
    - 79-381 - 79-382, 825 (Box 19)
- 9. Environmental Folders, 9; 2 linear feet 20 - 21 826 - 887
  Documents and clippings organized and collected by the Hudson River Environmental Society pertaining to environmental issues throughout the Hudson River Valley.
  Alphabetical
  - Environmental s, Box 20; 9
    Environmental s A-M
    - Central Hudson (1), 826 (Box 20)
    - Central Hudson (2), 827 (Box 20)
    - Central Hudson 1984 Danskammer & Roseton, 828 (Box 20)
    - Columbia Land Conservancy, 829 (Box 20)
    - Development, 830 (Box 20)
    - DCCC for Environmental Protection - Planning, 831 (Box 20)
    - Dutchess County Environmental Association, 832 (Box 20)
    - Dutchess County Environmental Council, 833 (Box 20)
    - Dutchess County Land Conservancy, 834 (Box 20)
    - Dutchess County Planning Federation (Newsletter), 835 (Box 20)
    - Dutchess - Garbage, 836 (Box 20)
    - Environment, 837 (Box 20)
    - Energy Conservation, 838 (Box 20)
    - Environmental Bond Act 1986, 839 (Box 20)
    - (The) Environmental Fund, 840 (Box 20)
    - Environmental Quality Index, 841 (Box 20)
    - Eweson System - Sewage, 842 (Box 20)
    - Farmland - Agriculture, 843 (Box 20)
    - Green Times, 844 (Box 20)
    - Historic Hudson Valley 1987, 845 (Box 20)
    - Hudson Highlands Larson Report 1977, 846 (Box 20)
    - Hudson River Bridges, 847 (Box 20)
    - Hudson River Lighthouse, 848 (Box 20)
    - Hudson River Valley Greenway 1992, 849 (Box 20)
    - Hudson River Valley Greenway 1993, 850 (Box 20)
    - Hudson River Valley Greenway 1994, 851 (Box 20)
    - Hudson River Valley Greenway 1995, 852 (Box 20)
    - Hudson River Valley Greenway 1996, 853 (Box 20)
    - Hudson River Valley Greenway 1997, 854 (Box 20)
    - Hudson River Valley Greenway 1998, 855 (Box 20)
    - Hudsonia, Millbrook Marsh, 856 (Box 20)
    - Landmarks Conservancy, 857 (Box 20)
    - Lower Hudson Conference, 858 (Box 20)
    - Minnewaska, 859 (Box 20)
  - Environmental s, Box 21; 9
    Environmental s N-Z
    - NY League of Conservation Voters, 860 (Box 21)
    - Patterns for Progress, 861 (Box 21)
    - Patterns for Progress Fall 1990 Newsletter, 862 (Box 21)
    - Patterns for Progress Membership Memos (1), 863 (Box 21)
    - Patterns for Progress Membership Memos (2), 864 (Box 21)
    - PLACE 1981-1982, 865 (Box 21)
    - PLACE 1983-1985, 866 (Box 21)
    - Preservation League of NYS Correspondence, 867 (Box 21)
    - Preservation League of NYS Newsletter Vol. 2-5, 868 (Box 21)
    - Preservation League of NYS Newsletter Vol. 6-17, 869 (Box 21)
    - Preservation League of NYS Preservation News, 870 (Box 21)
    - Preservation League of NYS Technical Series, 871 (Box 21)
    - Public Power, 872 (Box 21)
    - Quebec, James Bay - Cabot, 873 (Box 21)
    - Real Estate Re-Use, 874 (Box 21)
    - Recycling, 875 (Box 21)
    - Regional Planning, 876 (Box 21)
    - Regional Planning Assoc., 877 (Box 21)
    - Shorewalkers, 878 (Box 21)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restoration, 879 (Box 21)
    - S.O.R.E. (Save Our Rural Environment), 880 (Box 21)
    - Tri-State Regional Planning Commission, 881 (Box 21)
    - Water Pollution 1970, 882 (Box 21)
    - Water Pollution 1971-1978, 883 (Box 21)
    - Water Pollution 1979-1986, 884 (Box 21)
    - Water Pollution Misc., 885 (Box 21)
    - Watts De Peyster Fireman’s Hall, 886 (Box 21)
    - World Environment Day, 887 (Box 21)
- 10. Scenic Hudson Files, 10; 4.33 linear feet 22 - 26 888 - 1144
  Documents, negatives, and photographs from Scenic Hudson, Inc.
  - Office Files, 10.1
    - Office Files, Box 22; 10.1
      General files from Scenic Hudson
      - Challenge of the Hudson - Committee on Management 11/15/1990, 888 (Box 22)
      - Challenge of the Hudson Medal, 889 (Box 22)
      - Greenway Factsheets, 890 (Box 22)
      - Minutes 08/28/1990, 891 (Box 22)
      - Regatta, 892 (Box 22)
      - Regatta Guidelines, 893 (Box 22)
  - Storm King Files, 10.2
    - Storm King Files, Box 22; 10.2
      Correspondence, legal documents, and clippings related to Storm King
      - Answer in Opposition to Motion of Con Ed. to Terminate Hearings..., 894 (Box 22)
      - Answer of Con. Ed. to Scenic Hudson for a Stay of the Opinion and Order Issuing a License Herein, 895 (Box 22)
      - Aspects of the Early Life History of the Striped Bass..., 896 (Box 22)
      - Bills, 897 (Box 22)
      - Brief on Exceptions of the Scenic Hudson Preservation Conference, 898 (Box 22)
      - Clippings, 1964, 899 (Box 22)
      - Clippings, 1965, 900 (Box 22)
      - Clippings, Not Dated, 901 (Box 22)
      - Constitution and By-Laws and Certificate of Incorporation of the Hudson River Conservation Society Inc., 902 (Box 22)
      - Correspondence, 1963-06/1964, 903 (Box 22)
      - Correspondence, 07/1964-12/1964, 904 (Box 22)
      - Correspondence, 1965, 905 (Box 22)
      - Correspondence, Not Dated, 906 (Box 22)
      - Dues, 907 (Box 22)
      - Economic Evaluation, 908 (Box 22)
      - (the) Hudson River for Whose Utility?, 909 (Box 22)
      - Initial Brief to the Examiner of the Scenic Hudson Conference, 910 (Box 22)
      - Legal Correspondence, 911 (Box 22)
      - Maps (legal size), 912 (Box 22)
      - Misc. Documents (legal size), 913 (Box 22)
      - Order Setting Further Hearing, 914 (Box 22)
      - Petition, 915 (Box 22)
      - Petition for Hearing and Order Regulating Operation, 916 (Box 22)
      - Press Release, 917 (Box 22)
      - Progress Reports, 918 (Box 22)
      - Questions on HR 3012, 919 (Box 22)
      - Report, 920 (Box 22)
      - Reports, 921 (Box 22)
      - Scenic Hudson News, 922 (Box 22)
      - Statements, 923 (Box 22)
      - Testimony, 924 (Box 22)
  - Negatives, 10.3
    - Scenic Hudson – Negatives, Box 23; 10.3
      Scenic Hudson Negatives A-L
      - Babbit at Olana (PCB Briefing), 925 (Box 23)
      - Balloon Flying, 926 (Box 23)
      - Baltimore, 927 (Box 23)
      - Base of Mt. Beacon, 928 (Box 23)
      - Base of Storm King, 929 (Box 23)
      - Canoe Expedition through Ramshorn, 930 (Box 23)
      - Con Hook, 931 (Box 23)
      - Education: Esopus Meadows; Land Preservation - Four Mile Point, 932 (Box 23)
      - Education: Schools, 933 (Box 23)
      - Education: Schools - Vassar, 934 (Box 23)
      - Harbor Seal in Albany, 935 (Box 23)
      - Historic: Cultural Sites, 936 (Box 23)
      - Historic: Lighthouse, Poughkeepsie, 937 (Box 23)
      - Historic: Octagon House, 938 (Box 23)
      - Historic: Olana Dedication Viewshed Maker, 939 (Box 23)
      - Historic: Olana Viewshed, 940 (Box 23)
      - Hudson River Honored as American Heritage River, 941 (Box 23)
      - Hudson Valley Greenway Council, 942 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Beacon-Newburgh Waterfront, 943 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Beacon Waterfront, 944 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Beacon Waterfront, Esopus Meadows Point, 945 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Beacon Waterfront Revitilization, 946 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Black Creek, 947 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Black Creek Grand Opening, 948 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Black Creek, Lighthouses, Baltimore Waterfront, Sleightsburgh Spit, 949 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Black Creek Trail Building, 950 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Bridges, 951 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Burger Hill, 952 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Burger Hill Trailmasters’ Day, 953 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Clausland Mountain, 954 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Con Ed Lands - Red Hook/Clermont, 955 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Dominican Camp, 956 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Esopus Meadows, 957 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Esopus Meadows Park, Black Creek, & Shaupeneak Ridge, 958 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Esopus Meadows Point Preserve, 959 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Foundry Cove, 960 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Foundry Cove Historic Preserve, 961 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Foundry Cove Trail, Black Creek, 962 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Foundry Dock Park, 963 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Four Mile Point, 964 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Four Mile Point, Cahote Preserve, Ramshorn-Livingston Sanctuary, 965 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: General, Black Creek (photographs also), 966 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: General Columbia County, 967 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: General Dominican Camp, 968 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Gomez Mill House, 969 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: High Tor Vineyards, 970 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: HiTor, 971 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Hudson Highlands Southern Gateway Project, 972 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Hyde Park, 973 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Internegs - Dick’s Castle, 974 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Irvington Waterfront, 975 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Kingston/Tilcon Waterfront Property, 976 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Madam Brett Mill Park, 977 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Madam Brett Park, 978 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Moodna Creek Marsh, 979 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Moodna Creek/Nicoll Homestead, 980 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Mt. Beacon, 981 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Newburgh/Beacon Waterfront, 982 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Newburgh Waterfront, Mt. Beacon, 983 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Olana, 984 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Open Space Hearings, 985 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Osborn, Philipstown, 986 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Poets’ Walk Park, 987 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Rams Horn - Livingston Sanctuary, 988 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Riverfronts/Lakefronts, 989 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Shaupeneak Ridge, 990 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Shaupeneak Ridge, Madam Brett Mill Park, the Great River Sweep, 991 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Sleightsburgh Park, 992 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Sleightsburgh Park, Four Mile Point, 993 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Sleightsburgh Park, Esopus Meadows, Shaupeneak Ridge, 994 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Vanderbough Cove, Ramshore Marsh, 995 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Storm King School Project, 996 (Box 23)
      - Land Preservation: Weyant/Ft. Montgomery, 997 (Box 23)
      - Lighthouse Park, 998 (Box 23)
    - Scenic Hudson – Negatives, Box 24; 10.3
      Scenic Hudson Negatives M-So
      - Madam Brett Mill Park, 999 (Box 24)
      - Madam Brett Ribbon Cutting, 1000 (Box 24)
      - Miscellaneous: Buildings, 1001 (Box 24)
      - Miscellaneous: Events - Indoor (1), 1002 (Box 24)
      - Miscellaneous: Events - Indoor (2), 1003 (Box 24)
      - Miscellaneous: Events - Indoor (3), 1004 (Box 24)
      - Miscellaneous: Events - Outdoor (1), 1005 (Box 24)
      - Miscellaneous: Events - Outdoor (2), 1006 (Box 24)
      - Miscellaneous: Events - Outdoor (3), 1007 (Box 24)
      - Miscellaneous: Events - Outdoor (4), 1008 (Box 24)
      - Miscellaneous: from Ron..., 1009 (Box 24)
      - Miscellaneous: Landscapes (1), 1010 (Box 24)
      - Miscellaneous: Landscapes (2), 1011 (Box 24)
      - Newsletter Fall 1997 Cover Page, 1012 (Box 24)
      - Nyack Condos, 1013 (Box 24)
      - Palisades Interstate Parkway, 1014 (Box 24)
      - Peekskill Incinerator, 1015 (Box 24)
      - People, 1016 (Box 24)
      - People: Andrew Bicking, 1017 (Box 24)
      - People: Board and Staff 1997, 1018 (Box 24)
      - People: Christina Junta, Margaret Sestrom, Rich Schiago, Michelle Terwilliger, 1019 (Box 24)
      - People: Christopher Davis, 1020 (Box 24)
      - People: Former Employees; Land Preservation - General, 1021 (Box 24)
      - People: Franny & Wint 1996, 1022 (Box 24)
      - People: Jeff A. and Seth McKee, 1023 (Box 24)
      - People: Josh Cleland, 1024 (Box 24)
      - People: Klara B. Sauer, 1025 (Box 24)
      - People: Klara Sauer, David Redden, 1026 (Box 24)
      - People: Klara Sauer, David Redden, Sam Pryor, Betsy Pugh, 1027 (Box 24)
      - People: Maryann, Grace Rosemary, 1028 (Box 24)
      - People: Morrison Heckseler, 1029 (Box 24)
      - People: Ned Worthrop, 1030 (Box 24)
      - People: Program Staff 1988, 1031 (Box 24)
      - People: Program Staff - Board Members, 1032 (Box 24)
      - People: Staff 1991, 1033 (Box 24)
      - People: Staff 1993-1994, 1034 (Box 24)
      - People: Staff - Group Shots 1997, 1035 (Box 24)
      - People: Staff - Group Shots 1998, 1036 (Box 24)
      - People: Staff - Group Shots 1999, 1037 (Box 24)
      - People: Staff - Klara B. Sauer, 1038 (Box 24)
      - People: Young Friends, 1039 (Box 24)
      - People: Young Friends; Land Preservation: Shaupeneak Ridge, Esopus Meadows, 1040 (Box 24)
      - Printing/Publication: “Hudson Valley” June 1994 Cover Page, 1041 (Box 24)
      - Problem Areas: Alsen Coal Terminal/Mines, 1042 (Box 24)
      - Problem Areas: Cell Towers, 1043 (Box 24)
      - Problem Areas: Signs (good and bad), 1044 (Box 24)
      - Problem Areas: Visual Impacts, 1045 (Box 24)
      - Problem Areas: Water Quality, 1046 (Box 24)
      - Scenic River Vistas, 1047 (Box 24)
      - Shad Fishing, 1048 (Box 24)
      - Sotheby’s Exterior, 1049 (Box 24)
    - Scenic Hudson – Negatives, Box 25; 10.3
      Scenic Hudson Negatives Sp-Z
      - Special Events: American Heritage Initiatives, 1050 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: American Heritage River, 1051 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: American Heritage Rivers Initiative, 1052 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Beacon Countryside Exchange (1), 1053 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Beacon Countryside Exchange (2), 1054 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Birdathon 1996, 1055 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Birdathon Donation, 1056 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Birdwatchers 1996, 1057 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Board of Directors Retreat, 1058 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Bruce Babbitts Visit, 1059 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Burger Hill Park Opening, 1060 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Challenge of the Hudson, 1061 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Check Presentation, 1062 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Christmas Party 1997, 1063 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Env. Center Opening, 1064 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Estuary Action Program, 1065 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Eve’s Point Celebration, 1066 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Fishkill Ridge Hike, 1067 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: (the) Great River Sweep 1999, 1068 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: (the) Great River Sweep 2000, 1069 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Greenway Conference, 1070 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Greenway Signing at Mills Mansion, 1071 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Hermez Benefit, 1072 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Hillpoint Project Preservation Hike and Picnic, 1073 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Hiking Hyde Park Trail Management Committee, 1074 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Historic Survey, 1075 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Hudson River Stewardship Society Tea, 1076 (Box 25)